{
    "subject": "resource/Shade_Empire",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Shade Empire",
    "human_readable": "The name of Shade Empire is Shade Empire.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9744222164154053,
            "question": "What is the name of Shade Empire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8971811532974243,
            "question": "Does the name 'Shade Empire' have any particular meaning?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8875493407249451,
            "question": "Are there any other names associated with Shade Empire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8291935920715332,
            "question": "What might be the history of Shade Empire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8096128702163696,
            "question": "Is Shade Empire a real place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7869086861610413,
            "question": "What kind of things might exist in Shade Empire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7382757067680359,
            "question": "Who or what might govern Shade Empire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6998171806335449,
            "question": "Could Shade Empire be fictional?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.610065221786499,
            "question": "If Shade Empire is fictional, what genre could it belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46832409501075745,
            "question": "Could Shade Empire inspire a story or artwork?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Shade Empire is Shade Empire.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4393_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If Shade Empire is fictional, what genre could it belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4393_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could Shade Empire be fictional?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4393_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who or what might govern Shade Empire?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4393_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4393_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4393_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4393_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4393_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4393_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4393_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4393_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4393_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4393_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4393_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}